I'm actually in a mentorship myself,
and we've always been told, "Never tell
someone the price until you get on the
call with them." And what I sell is
high-ticket coaching.
How much is it?
What, in pounds or dirhams? [chuckles]
Pounds.
Pounds. The minimum is £360 a month.
Okay. It's not that crazy.
It's not that crazy,
but then the higher ticket
is like 710 in a month.
Okay. Still,
I don't think that's too crazy.
Yeah.
And what's your conversion rate on the
sales calls?
I mean,
eight out of 10.
Okay, cool.
So I've got a high conversion rate.
But I would never tell someone a price
because they just wouldn't see the value
in
it.
And any time I ever have told somebody the
price, if they really
push for it on Instagram DMs,
then I would tell them,
and then they'll be like,
"Mm,
nah," because they don't see the value.
So I'm really interested to understand
your mindset
behind why you would do that. Is
that because of your kind of you're up
there and I'm down there-
No, not-
... you can afford to kind of just go,
"Fuck you"?
Well, first of all,
I wouldn't sell in DMs.
I don't talk to people in DMs, really.
Okay.
I think that if you're--
So let's imagine this.
Let's look at a product
that I would consider.
Do you use an Eight Sleep at all?
Sorry?
Eight Sleep. Do you know what that is?
Who or what?
Eight Sleep.
Anyone in here got an Eight Sleep?
A what?
So an Eight Sleep is a
temperature-controlled mattress cover.
Oh, yeah. I do know what you mean.
My friend's got one, yeah.
Cool, yeah. So, I bought an Eight Sleep.
It was like £4,000.
Yeah.
Right? For a mattress cover.
And at first, I was like, "Oh, is
that worth it?" I got onto the website.
They didn't want to do a sales call.
They just told me all the features of it,
had some nice branding, and then offered
me a 30-day money-back guarantee.
They then sent me 85 kilograms worth of
kit.
Because I've got the bed frame,
the thing that sits you up.
I've got the mattress cover.
I've got the pod.
I've got the water filter.
I've got everything.
They sent me all of that.
Now, if I send it back to them,
they can't sell it.
So they've just sent me thousands of
pounds of equipment
that weighs nearly as much
as me on the premise
that I can just send it back to them
and get my money back.
Now, when I went on the website,
I got to see the product,
see the benefits, see
everything about it,
and I made a decision then whether
or not to buy or not.
And for me,
I didn't need to jump on a call with
someone for four grand.
And that's not just because the level I'm
at, it's also because they gave me a
money-back guarantee. I
was either a happy customer
or I got my money back.
So when you give people those things,
which will be hard in the DMs, because
if you
try portraying the value, what I get,
why I need it, what it costs, and why to
trust you,
it's the wrong fucking place to do that.
The same way that in Hinge,
you only talk to someone to arrange a
date, and you get
into the knit and gritty face to face.
So with that in mind,
do you have a website with all the offer
and
everything there and everything?
Yeah, I do have a website, but the
offer's not there, no.
Because what I would say is you
are an active website.
You are being a website every time you
call someone up.
Yeah.
And you are giving your time
and energy and effort to do that.
For me, I'll be perfectly honest,
my reason for it is I fucking hate phone
calls.
So do I. [chuckles]
But you're doing them, right?
Yeah.
So every time a sales call comes in-
I do. Yeah
... do you get excited about it?
Sorry, what?
If I said there's a magical button here,
if we press it, you never have to call
someone ever again, would you press it?
Yeah, of course.
Then why not?
The sales call works because it's what
you're doing all the time, and
you're manually getting there
and calling people
and going through everything.
But in my mind, I'm like,
if we can sell a 4,000-pound mattress
cover that regulates your temperature,
why can't we sell £360 worth of
coaching where they can go,
they can see the results,
they can go through it at
their own pace.
Because ultimately as well,
I don't particularly want to get on a
call with someone as a consumer
or as someone running a
business. It works. That's the problem,
right?
It works.
That's why you might feel like it works.
But also,
the pricing thing to me just feels a bit
deceptive.
Imagine I'm like, "Oh,
you've got to come to this hotel in Dubai.
It's called the Atlantis." "How much
is it?" "Come to the hotel." "No, no,
but how
much?" "You come to the hotel.
Tell you what, stay three nights,
we'll talk
when you get here."
And then you get to the reception,
you get there, and you're
like, "What?
It's two grand a night." Now suddenly,
I feel like I've wasted
everyone's time,
and I'm fucking embarrassed.
I might just book a room in the hotel
because I'm embarrassed.
I might be like, "Well, fuck,
I'm here." I've done it before,
where you're in a
shop and you buy something.
You didn't realize how much expensive it
was, but
you're at the till now, so you're like,
"Oh, fuck, I best buy it." So for me, I
just don't ever want that.
And I want people to know I'm expensive.
I want people to know it's a lot of money.
Eight Sleep don't give a fuck their
mattress is four grand because all the
people
that can't afford it are talking about it,
and all the people that can afford it
can. So again,
you can do the sales calls if you want,
but you
just told me you didn't enjoy it.
And every part of your business,
I want you to
love. And ultimately,
if I could free up those hours from your
life
and give you a mechanism
that gets people to visit a website,
ultimately, all I ever do,
my whole business is sending people to
websites.
I don't want any feedback of people
that don't buy.
So I've never done a sales call for my
mentorship, done millions of dollars.
Never done a sales call for my coaching
app, done millions of dollars.
Had 100,000 people use my app,
never done a sales call.
For me, I want to build something
that I love.
I fucking barely get on a phone call for
$1,000 now.
Even then, I'm like, "Oh,
I've got a call in the morning." I hate
it.
I want to build a whole infrastructure
that only every part of it I love.
And I think you should show pricing.
Are you good at what you do?
Yes.
Then why is it a problem?
The Lamborghini Sterrato, it doesn't say,
"Come to the showroom and I'll show
you." They're like, "No,
it's $600,000." Like, "Oh, fuck,
must be good." So,
I would only ever say
that maybe you would have a traffic
problem.
And again, we could disagree.
But like I said, I asked you if there
was a button we
could press and the sales calls go away,
you would press it.
So I would work to do that.
Or even better yet,
show your pricing on your landing page,
give them everything they need,
get them to buy then at
that point with the money-back guarantee.
Then at the worst-case scenario,
if you really need to, book
a call.
Because then you could just write an
email, hit send,
wake up in the morning and
go, "Fucking hell,
I made money last night."
Okay.
And we can fight about it. We can argue.
[chuckles]
But to me,
I will never get on a sales call because I
could never
imagine anything worse than spending 45
minutes with someone
for them to say, "Nah."
Because two out of 10 of people
that you do do that,
and they go, "Oh, sounds lovely.
Thanks for that." Then they put the Zoom
call
down. You never hear from them again.
[groans]
Imagine getting feedback of all the people
that swipe no to you on Hinge.
[groans] For me, I just don't like that.
Maybe I'm insecure.
But yeah. Does that help?
Yeah. Thank you.
Cool.